http://raystevens.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS DESIGNED TO INFORM YOU ABOUT THE INFORMATION RAYSTEVENS.COM COLLECTS AT THIS WEBSITE, WHY WE COLLECT SUCH INFORMATION, AND HOW WE WILL HANDLE INFORMATION WE LEARN ABOUT YOU FROM YOUR VISIT TO OUR WEBSITE. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR ASSENT TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE.
WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, AT OUR COMPLETE DISCRETION, TO CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD, OR REMOVE PORTIONS OF THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME; HOWEVER, WE WILL NOT RETROACTIVELY CHANGE HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT. PLEASE CHECK BACK PERIODICALLY FOR ANY CHANGES WE MAY MAKE TO THE POLICY, AS YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS SITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THESE TERMS WILL MEAN YOU ACCEPT THESE CHANGES. WE URGE YOU TO READ THE COMPLETE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW, AS WELL AS OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
Personal Information We Collect
We may ask you for your first name, last name, e-mail address, birth date or age, street address, city, state, zip code, mobile or other telephone number. We may also ask for your comments, suggestions, or other information relating to our site, our products or services, or the company. Other specific types of information may be requested in connection with contests, sweepstakes, other promotional offers or other marketing efforts. Also, your e-mail address and/or your domain name will be automatically recognized when you visit our site.
Our primary purpose in gathering this personal information is to enter you in contests and sweepstakes and notify you of results, send you current RayStevens.com information or offers (if you have given us permission to do so), and fulfill your requests, or for other purposes as described when you submit your information.
Other Information We Collect
Cookies are used within this site. A “cookie” is a small file that we save on your computer’s hard drive that contains non-personal information. Our cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited, allow you to personalize your pages, and help you to participate in activities or events on the site. They also assist us in customizing our offerings to you. If you leave the site and then return, cookies will tell us what things you have already collected so that you do not have to start all over again. Cookies store multi-page data entry until data is submitted to a database (i.e., in connection with an extensive poll or survey), and prevent further participation in a poll or survey by a particular browser. At sites that offer shopping, cookies keep track of items in your shopping cart. Cookies do not contain any personal information about a specific user, and we do not use cookies or other non-consensual methods to take personally identifiable or online contact information about you off of your computer. We do not use cookies for direct marketing or promotional purposes, and cookies are not used at this site to collect information specifically about you for sharing with third parties. We also use other technology, called clear GIFs, to provide us with other important anonymous information, such as when an e-mail has been opened.
Sharing of Personal Information
We want to be very clear: We do not obtain personal information about you at this site other than that which you choose to provide, and we will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose the personal information you provide us to anyone outside of RayStevens.com or its advertising and promotional agencies and consultants for their commercial marketing purposes, except in those specific instances where you expressly give us permission to do so. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to collect, use, and disclose any information, including but not limited to, personally identifiable information, we may deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any law, regulation, legal request, or government request. Without assuming any obligation to do so, we also reserve the right to collect and share any information we deem necessary to investigate or take action in connection with suspected fraud, illegal activities, possible harm to persons or property, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
How to Contact Us
If you no longer wish to receive offers or information from this site, if you would like to obtain a copy of the personal information gathered by this website, or if you would like to correct or delete such information from our website’s marketing database, you can always send us an e-mail with your concern or question by visiting our CONTACT section of RayStevens.com.
Special Notice to California Residents
Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to RayStevens.com including the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line, and provide us with your name, address, and e-mail address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.
Thank you for visiting our site.
Effective Date: This policy was last updated on May 25th to reflect GDPR for EU.
